My Little Pony: Equestria Girls - Forgotten Friendship is a
animation, family, fantasy film directed by Ishi Rudell.
The story follows Sunset Shimmer, who (using her powers) finds out that her friends'
memories of her have been mysteriously erased, resulting in them getting amnesia.
Determined to set things straight, she'll need Princess Twilight's help from Equestria
in order to find out the source of what caused her friends' memory loss.
Sunset Shimmer /  Twilight Sparkle (singing voice), played by Rebecca Shoichet.
Applejack / Rainbow Dash / Nurse Redheart (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy (voice), played by Andrea Libman.
Rarity / Princess Luna / Vice Principal Luna
(voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Twilight Sparkle / Princess Twilight Sparkle (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Trixie Lulamoon (voice), played by Kathleen Barr.
My Little Pony: Equestria Girls – Forgotten Friendship (alternatively subtitled Most Likely to be Forgotten on the YouTube release) is a 2018 animated
television special within Hasbro's My Little Pony: Equestria Girls franchise, itself a spin-off of the 2010 relaunch of the My Little Pony toy line.
The special was directed by Ishi Rudell and Katrina Hadley, written and edited by Nick
Confalone, and produced by DHX Media Vancouver for Hasbro Studios in the United States.
Premiered on Discovery Family (a joint venture between Discovery Communications and Hasbro) on February 17, 2018, it is the first one-hour Equestria Girls special,
preceding Rollercoaster of Friendship (released later in July), Spring Breakdown (2019), Sunset's Backstage Pass (2019), and Holidays Unwrapped (2019).